[
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: It's been an hour and not one of my classmates has shown up! I tell you, when I actually die some people are gonna get seriously haunted!",
   "Speaker 2: There you go! Someone came!",
   "Speaker 1: Ok, ok! I'm gonna go hide! Oh, this is so exciting, my first mourner!",
   "Speaker 3: Hi, glad you could come.",
   "Speaker 2: Please, come in.",
   "Speaker 4: Hi, you're Chandler Bing, right? I'm Tom Gordon, I was in your class.",
   "Speaker 2: Oh yes, yes... let me... take your coat.",
   "Speaker 4: Thanks... uh... I'm so sorry about Ross, it's...",
   "Speaker 2: At least he died doing what he loved... watching blimps.",
   "Speaker 1: Who is he?",
   "Speaker 2: Some guy, Tom Gordon.",
   "Speaker 1: I don't remember him, but then again I touched so many lives.",
   "Speaker 3: So, did you know Ross well?",
   "Speaker 4: Oh, actually I barely knew him. Yeah, I came because I heard Chandler's news. D'you know if he's seeing anyone?",
   "Speaker 3: Yes, he is. Me.",
   "Speaker 4: What? You... You... Oh! Can I ask you a personal question? Ho-how do you shave your beard so close?",
   "Speaker 2: Ok Tommy, that's enough mourning for you! Here we go, bye bye!!",
   "Speaker 4: Hey, listen. Call me.",
   "Speaker 2: Ok!"
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "Tommy",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Chandler Bing",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 4",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     4
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alumni"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Tommy",
    "x": "Speaker 4",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Tom Gordon",
    "x": "Speaker 4",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 2",
    "x": "Speaker 4",
    "rid": [
     4,
     1
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alumni",
     "per:positive_impression"
    ],
    "t": [
     "",
     "call me"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: So, eh... it's probably gonna be hard for you to leave Boston, huh?",
   "Speaker 2: Actually, I'm kinda happy to be leaving... I just broke up with someone.",
   "Speaker 1: Ooh... so sad... Still, it can't be easy for you to leave Harvard? Especially after working alongside a Nobel Prize winner like Albert Wintermeyer?",
   "Speaker 2: Actually, Alby is the guy I broke up with.",
   "Speaker 1: You... you dated Albert Wintermeyer?",
   "Speaker 2: Yeah...",
   "Speaker 1: ... And you called him Alby!? I mean that's like... like calling Albert Einstein... er... Alby...",
   "Speaker 2: Yeah, well, he is a brilliant man.",
   "Speaker 1: Eh, you think? I mean, you went out with a guy who improved the accuracy of radiocarbon dating by a factor of 10!",
   "Speaker 2: Yes! And while that is everything one looks for in a boyfriend, he had a lot of issues...",
   "Speaker 1: Oh! like what?! Oh I'm sorry, I don't mean to pry... it's just that this must be what regular people experience when they watch \"Access Hollywood\".",
   "Speaker 2: Ok, you want the dirt? Alby was seriously insecure. I mean, he was really intimidated by the guy I dated before him.",
   "Speaker 1: Who is intimidating to a guy who won the Nobel Prize?",
   "Speaker 2: A guy who won two.",
   "Speaker 1: Two? Wha...? Don't tell me you dated Benjamin Hobart",
   "Speaker 2: Yeah... for three years.",
   "Speaker 1: Oh my God! Have you ever been in a relationship with someone who hasn't won the Nobel Prize?",
   "Speaker 2: ... no... bu but there was my first boyfriend Billy.",
   "Speaker 1: Oh yeah? no, no Nobel Prizes for him?",
   "Speaker 2: No, but he did just win the McArthur genius grant.",
   "Speaker 1: Huh... huh... what a loser! Some more wine?"
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "Benjamin Hobart",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     10
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:girl/boyfriend"
    ],
    "t": [
     "relationship"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Boston",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     18
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:place_of_residence"
    ],
    "t": [
     "leave"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "GPE"
   },
   {
    "y": "Harvard",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     22
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:employee_or_member_of"
    ],
    "t": [
     "leave"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "ORG"
   },
   {
    "y": "Billy",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     10
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:girl/boyfriend"
    ],
    "t": [
     "first boyfriend"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Albert Wintermeyer",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     10
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:girl/boyfriend"
    ],
    "t": [
     "broke up with"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Alby",
    "x": "Albert Wintermeyer",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Nobel Prize winner",
    "x": "Albert Wintermeyer",
    "rid": [
     29
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:title"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 2",
    "x": "Albert Wintermeyer",
    "rid": [
     10
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:girl/boyfriend"
    ],
    "t": [
     "broke up with"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "a loser",
    "x": "Billy",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 2",
    "x": "Billy",
    "rid": [
     10
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:girl/boyfriend"
    ],
    "t": [
     "first boyfriend"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 2",
    "x": "Harvard",
    "rid": [
     35
    ],
    "r": [
     "org:employees_or_members"
    ],
    "t": [
     "leave"
    ],
    "x_type": "ORG",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 2",
    "x": "Boston",
    "rid": [
     32
    ],
    "r": [
     "gpe:residents_of_place"
    ],
    "t": [
     "leave"
    ],
    "x_type": "GPE",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 2",
    "x": "Benjamin Hobart",
    "rid": [
     10
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:girl/boyfriend"
    ],
    "t": [
     "relationship"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "man",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "loser",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "Albert Wintermeyer",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     1
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:positive_impression"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: Hi!",
   "Speaker 2: Hi!",
   "Speaker 1: So umm, what's this book about?",
   "Speaker 2: You didn't read this one either?!",
   "Speaker 1: Well, I was gonna, but I accidentally read something else.",
   "Speaker 2: What?",
   "Speaker 1: Vogue! Hey, so tell me about this Jane Eyre woman.",
   "Speaker 2: No! You should've read it yourself!",
   "Speaker 1: Come on Phoebe! Don’t be such a goodie-goodie!",
   "Speaker 2: Fine! Okay, all right, so Jane Eyre, first of all, you'd think she's a woman, but she's not. She's a cyborg.",
   "Speaker 1: A cyborg?! Isn't that like a robot?!",
   "Speaker 2: Yeah, this book was light years ahead of its time.",
   "Speaker 3: Sorry I'm late. Let's get started. So, what did everybody think about Jane Eyre?",
   "Speaker 2: Umm, Rachel and I were just discussing it and she had some very interesting insights.",
   "Speaker 3: Well, go ahead Rachel.",
   "Speaker 1: Uh, thank you Phoebe. Umm, well, what struck me most when reading Jane Eyre was uh, how the book was so ahead of its time.",
   "Speaker 3: If you're talking about feminism, I think you're right.",
   "Speaker 1: Yeah, well, feminism yes, but also the robots."
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "goodie-goodie",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: Hi.",
   "Speaker 2: Hi.",
   "Speaker 1: I just finished getting Phoebe all dressed to meet Mike's parents. She's so nervous, it's so sweet!",
   "Speaker 2: Guess what? I made Emma laugh today.",
   "Speaker 1: You WHAT? And I missed it? Because I was giving a makeover to that stupid hippie?",
   "Speaker 2: Yeah, and it was uhm... it was like a real little person laugh too. It was... it was like uhm... Only... only not creepy.",
   "Speaker 1: Well... well, what did you do to make her laugh?",
   "Speaker 2: I uhm... Well, I sang... well actually I rapped... Baby Got Back...",
   "Speaker 1: You WHAT? You sang... to our baby daughter... a song about a guy who likes to have sex with women with giant asses?",
   "Speaker 2: But you know what, if you think about it, it actually promotes a healthy uhm... body image... because... even big butts or uhm... juicy doubles.",
   "Speaker 1: owwwww...",
   "Speaker 2: Please don't take her away from me!"
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "Phoebe",
    "x": "Mike",
    "rid": [
     10
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:girl/boyfriend"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Baby",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "Emma",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     13
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:children"
    ],
    "t": [
     "baby daughter"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Baby Got Back",
    "x": "Emma",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     "laugh"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 1",
    "x": "Emma",
    "rid": [
     15
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:parents"
    ],
    "t": [
     "baby daughter"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 2",
    "x": "Emma",
    "rid": [
     15
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:parents"
    ],
    "t": [
     "baby daughter"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Mike",
    "x": "Phoebe",
    "rid": [
     10
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:girl/boyfriend"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Baby",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "Emma",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     13
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:children"
    ],
    "t": [
     "baby daughter"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: 'Okay. Okay, daddy we'll see you tomorrow night. Okay bye-bye.'",
   "Speaker 2: We?",
   "Speaker 1: Are ah, having dinner with my Dad tomorrow night, I hope that's okay.",
   "Speaker 2: Oh shoot, tomorrow's not so good, I'm supposed to um, fall off the Empire State building and land on a bicycle with no seat. Sorry.",
   "Speaker 1: Ross, my father doesn't hate you.",
   "Speaker 2: Please, he refers to me as 'wethead'.",
   "Speaker 1: But honey he calls everybody by a nickname! Okay, look, I know, all right, just one dinner, please, just one night for me, please. I just want him to love you like I do."
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "honey",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 2",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     1,
     10
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:positive_impression",
     "per:girl/boyfriend"
    ],
    "t": [
     "love",
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "honey",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "daddy",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 1",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     10
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:girl/boyfriend"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "wethead",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     "nickname"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: Hey Pheebs.",
   "Speaker 2: Hey!",
   "Speaker 1: Any sign of your brother?",
   "Speaker 2: No, but he's always late.",
   "Speaker 1: I thought you only met him once?",
   "Speaker 2: Yeah, I did. I think it sounds y'know big sistery, y'know, 'Frank's always late.'",
   "Speaker 1: Well relax, he'll be here."
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "Speaker 2",
    "x": "Frank",
    "rid": [
     16
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:siblings"
    ],
    "t": [
     "brother"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Pheebs",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Pheebs",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Frank",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     16
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:siblings"
    ],
    "t": [
     "brother"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: Monica.",
   "Speaker 2: Oh my God! He just said my name! Did you hear that?",
   "Speaker 1: Monica bang!",
   "Speaker 3: Okay, I heard that.",
   "Speaker 2: Did he just say 'Monica bang'?",
   "Speaker 3: Uh-huh.",
   "Speaker 2: Oh my God! He's gonna rat me out!",
   "Speaker 1: Monica bang!",
   "Speaker 2: Oh-ho-ho, sweetie, sweetie, you gotta stop saying that, now. It's no big deal, it's not even worth mentioning, you see we all do it all the time. See watch this, Ben, Ben, Ben. Ow, Monica bang! Everybody bang. Ben bang. Rachel bang. Bang, Rachel bang! Oh, isn't that fun?",
   "Speaker 3:  Look at that! Look at that! We all do it. Okay, I'm stopping now.",
   "Speaker 2: You okay?",
   "Speaker 3: Oh yeah! Y'know, if it's not a headboard, it's just not worth it."
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "Monica bang",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "sweetie",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "Rachel bang",
    "x": "Speaker 3",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "sweetie",
    "x": "Speaker 3",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "sweetie",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: Oh hey! Wait up!",
   "Speaker 2: Hi!",
   "Speaker 1: Congratulations! I didn't want to say anything in front of Joey because I didn't know if he knew yet.",
   "Speaker 2: What, that we had a baby? Come on let's give him a little credit, although he did eat a piece of plastic fruit earlier.",
   "Speaker 1: No! No, that you and Rachel are engaged!",
   "Speaker 2: What?",
   "Speaker 1: Oh, it's a secret. Oh goodie! Yes! We haven't done the secret thing in a long time.",
   "Speaker 2: Phoebe, there is no secret. Okay? I didn't propose.",
   "Speaker 1: Are you lying? Is this like that time you tried to convince us that you were a doctor?",
   "Speaker 2: I am a doctor! Y'know what? I'm just gonna go and talk to Rachel myself.",
   "Speaker 1: All right, me too. Should we wake her up?",
   "Speaker 2: No! No, come on let her sleep! She's so exhausted."
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "baby",
    "x": "Rachel",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "baby",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "baby",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "doctor",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     29
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:title"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: Over here Jack. OK. I see, Rachel's coming up the path. Oh doesn't she look pretty. Jack, get this.",
   "Speaker 2: Get a shot of Monica. Where's Monica.",
   "Speaker 3: Over here dad.",
   "Speaker 4: Wait, how do you zoom out? There she is.",
   "Speaker 3: Oh, you look so great.",
   "Speaker 5: Ahh, so do you, beautiful.",
   "Speaker 3: Oops.",
   "Speaker 5: What?",
   "Speaker 3: Shoot, I think I got mayonaise on you.",
   "Speaker 5: Oh, that's OK, it's just the shoulder, it's not my dress.",
   "Speaker 4: Everybody smile.",
   "Speaker 3: Oh, dad, turn it off.",
   "Speaker 4: It is off.",
   "Speaker 3: Dad, it is not. What's with the red light?",
   "Speaker 4: It's the off light. Right Ross?",
   "Speaker 6: You look pretty tonight.",
   "Speaker 5: Oh, thanks. So, uh, what are you gonna do this summer?",
   "Speaker 6: Oh, you know, I'm just gonna, I'm gonna hang out, work on my music.",
   "Speaker 5: Is my hook unhooked? These things keep falling down, I can't. . .",
   "Speaker 6: Uh, hold, let me see, I don't know. So what're you gonna do. . .",
   "Speaker 5: Oh, the guys are here.",
   "Speaker 6: this summer?"
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "Speaker 3",
    "x": "Speaker 4",
    "rid": [
     13
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:children"
    ],
    "t": [
     "dad"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Jack",
    "x": "Speaker 4",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 4",
    "x": "Speaker 3",
    "rid": [
     15
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:parents"
    ],
    "t": [
     "dad"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "beautiful",
    "x": "Speaker 3",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: Alright, wait a second, why would Ross tell everyone in your class that you are as... \"gay as the day is long\"?",
   "Speaker 2: Because I told everyone he slept with dinosaurs.",
   "Speaker 1: But that's clearly a joke. This could easily be true.",
   "Speaker 2: Would you get that please? People have been calling to congratulate me all day.",
   "Speaker 1: Hello? No, he's not here. Yeah, this is his wife. Yeah, well, it came as quite a shock to me too. I guess I should have known. Yeah, I mean, he just kept making me watch Moulin Rouge.",
   "Speaker 2: Hang up, hang up. And that was a great movie! I'm so gonna get back at Ross... oh yeah, this will show him, here we go.",
   "Speaker 1: What are you doing?",
   "Speaker 2: Oh, you'll see my friend."
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "Speaker 2",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     17
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:spouse"
    ],
    "t": [
     "wife"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "my friend",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "Moulin Rouge",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     1
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:positive_impression"
    ],
    "t": [
     "great movie"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 1",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     17
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:spouse"
    ],
    "t": [
     "wife"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "my friend",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "Ross",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     4
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alumni"
    ],
    "t": [
     "class"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 2",
    "x": "Ross",
    "rid": [
     4
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alumni"
    ],
    "t": [
     "class"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: I'll just wait to put your order in.",
   "Speaker 2: You guys are over an hour late. What happened to you two?",
   "Speaker 3: I'm so sorry ...",
   "Speaker 4: We got locked out of the apartment, we ...",
   "Speaker 5: That's a great story. Can I eat it?",
   "Speaker 3: And then Rachel wasn't sure she could leave the baby.",
   "Speaker 4: It wasn't easy, but it's your birthday and I did what I got to do.",
   "Speaker 2: And that's Judy over there at the bar with Emma?",
   "Speaker 4: Oh honey, this is for the best, this way I'm not distracted, worrying about Emma, how she's doing at home and I'm being completely here with you and, oh, she spit up!",
   "Speaker 3: What?",
   "Speaker 4: She spit up. Judy! She spi...Judy! Look alive, Judy! Thank you.",
   "Speaker 3: Thanks. Oh.",
   "Speaker 3: Rach, c'mon, Emma is fine. You're turning into an obsessive mother. Okay, you need to stop.",
   "Speaker 4: You guys ever heard the story about when Ross's mom went to the beauty salon?",
   "Speaker 6: You mean the willie story?",
   "Speaker 3: Huh-huh, they already know it!",
   "Speaker 2: You guys, we've been waiting for you for a long time, maybe you should order.",
   "Speaker 5: No, no, it's okay, I already told the waiter what they want.",
   "Speaker 7: Why would you do that?",
   "Speaker 5: Chandler, control your woman!",
   "Speaker 4: Okay, as everybody has ordered, I would like to start the celebration and make a toast ... to Phoebe. She dropped her sock.",
   "Speaker 2: Aw ... what?",
   "Speaker 4: No, no, Emma dropped her sock.",
   "Speaker 7: Mom's here? I wanted to have lunch with her today, she told me she was out of town.",
   "Speaker 4: Ross, she still has not noticed that the baby's sock is on the ground.",
   "Speaker 2: It's a good toast.",
   "Speaker 4: Could you please get her attention?",
   "Speaker 3: Mommy!"
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "honey",
    "x": "Speaker 7",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "Judy",
    "x": "Speaker 7",
    "rid": [
     15
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:parents"
    ],
    "t": [
     "Mom"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 3",
    "x": "Speaker 7",
    "rid": [
     16
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:siblings"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 4",
    "x": "Emma",
    "rid": [
     15
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:parents"
    ],
    "t": [
     "mother"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "honey",
    "x": "Speaker 4",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "Mommy",
    "x": "Speaker 4",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "Emma",
    "x": "Speaker 4",
    "rid": [
     13
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:children"
    ],
    "t": [
     "mother"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Rach",
    "x": "Speaker 4",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 7",
    "x": "Judy",
    "rid": [
     13
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:children"
    ],
    "t": [
     "Mom"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 3",
    "x": "Judy",
    "rid": [
     13
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:children"
    ],
    "t": [
     "Mommy"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "honey",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "honey",
    "x": "Speaker 5",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "honey",
    "x": "Speaker 6",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "honey",
    "x": "Speaker 3",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 7",
    "x": "Speaker 3",
    "rid": [
     16
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:siblings"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Judy",
    "x": "Speaker 3",
    "rid": [
     15
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:parents"
    ],
    "t": [
     "Mommy"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: Hi!",
   "Speaker 2: Hey! So what's the big news you had us rush all the way over here for?",
   "Speaker 3: Okay, our news. My company has asked me to head up our office in Tulsa , so as of Monday I'm being officially relocated.",
   "Speaker 2: Oh my God!",
   "Speaker 4: What?!",
   "Speaker 1: What?!",
   "Speaker 2: Monday?!",
   "Speaker 5: How long do you have to go for?",
   "Speaker 3: They said it could be up to a year.",
   "Speaker 5: A year?!",
   "Speaker 1: Do you have to go?",
   "Speaker 6: I kind of have to don't I? Because of this stupid thing.",
   "Speaker 3: There is nothing like the support of your loving wife, huh?",
   "Speaker 5: Wait a minute, you can't go to Tulsa. Maybe you forgot, but we've got tickets to the Jets game next week.",
   "Speaker 3: I'm sorry buddy, but I don't think I'm gonna be able to make it.",
   "Speaker 5: We were gonna go see the Jets!",
   "Speaker 2: You can't go, I mean you're the glue that holds this group together!",
   "Speaker 3: Really?",
   "Speaker 2: Not you.",
   "Speaker 5: I can't believe you guys are moving.",
   "Speaker 4: I call their apartment!!!",
   "Speaker 7: No!!! Ah!! Ahh!!!"
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "Speaker 3",
    "x": "Speaker 6",
    "rid": [
     17
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:spouse"
    ],
    "t": [
     "wife"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "buddy",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 6",
    "x": "Speaker 3",
    "rid": [
     17
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:spouse"
    ],
    "t": [
     "wife"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "buddy",
    "x": "Speaker 3",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "Jets",
    "x": "Speaker 5",
    "rid": [
     1
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:positive_impression"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "ORG"
   },
   {
    "y": "buddy",
    "x": "Speaker 5",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: I don't know what else to say.",
   "Speaker 2: Well that works out good, because I'm not listening.",
   "Speaker 1: I feel terrible, I really do.",
   "Speaker 2: Oh, I'm sorry, did my back hurt your knife?",
   "Speaker 1: Rachel, say that I'm friends with her, we spend some time together. Is that so terrible?",
   "Speaker 2: Yes.",
   "Speaker 1: It's that terrible?",
   "Speaker 2: Yes. Monica, you don't get it. It's bad enough that she's stolen the guy who might actually be the person that I am supposed to be with, but now, she's actually, but now she's actually stealing you.",
   "Speaker 1: Me? What are you talking about? Nobody could steal me from you. I mean, just because I'm friends with her doesn't make me any less friends with you. I mean, you're my...We're, we're...Oh, I love you.",
   "Speaker 2: I love you too.",
   "Speaker 3: You guys, um I know that this really doesn't have anything to do with me, but um I love you guys too. Oh, I really needed that.",
   "Speaker 1: Look, I know that you're in a place right now where you really need to hate Julie's guts, but she didn't do anything wrong. I mean, she was just a girl who met a guy, and now they go out. I really think that if you gave her a chance, you'd like her. Would you just give that a chance, for me?",
   "Speaker 2: I'd do anything for you, you know that.",
   "Speaker 1: I'd do anything for you.",
   "Speaker 3: Wait, wait, wait, wait!"
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "Julie",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     9
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:friends"
    ],
    "t": [
     "friends with"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 2",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     9,
     1
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:friends",
     "per:positive_impression"
    ],
    "t": [
     "friends",
     "love"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 1",
    "x": "Julie",
    "rid": [
     9
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:friends"
    ],
    "t": [
     "friends with"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 1",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     1,
     9
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:positive_impression",
     "per:friends"
    ],
    "t": [
     "love you",
     "friends"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 1",
    "x": "Speaker 3",
    "rid": [
     1
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:positive_impression"
    ],
    "t": [
     "love you guys"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 2",
    "x": "Speaker 3",
    "rid": [
     1
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:positive_impression"
    ],
    "t": [
     "love you guys"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: Hey buddy.",
   "Speaker 2: Uh, hi.",
   "Speaker 1: Um, can I come back in?",
   "Speaker 2: Why?",
   "Speaker 1: I, I was just thinking about how much more we have to talk about.",
   "Speaker 2: But you left."
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "Speaker 1",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     2
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:negative_impression"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "buddy",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: Yo, paisan! Can I talk to you for a sec? Your tailor is a very bad man!",
   "Speaker 2: Frankie? What're you talking about?",
   "Speaker 3: Hey, what's goin' on?",
   "Speaker 1: Joey's tailor...took advantage of me.",
   "Speaker 3: What?",
   "Speaker 2: No way. I've been going to the guy for 12 years."
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "tailor",
    "x": "Frankie",
    "rid": [
     29
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:title"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 1",
    "x": "Frankie",
    "rid": [
     7
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:client"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 2",
    "x": "Frankie",
    "rid": [
     7
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:client"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "man",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "paisan",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "man",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "Frankie",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     2
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:negative_impression"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "man",
    "x": "Speaker 3",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: Eddie, I didn't sleep with your ex-girlfriend.",
   "Speaker 2: That's very interesting, ya know, 'cause that's exactly what someone who slept with her would say.",
   "Speaker 1: This is nuts. This is crazy. She came over for like two minutes, dropped off a fish tank, and left, end of story.",
   "Speaker 2: Where's Buddy?",
   "Speaker 1: Buddy?",
   "Speaker 2: My fish, Buddy.",
   "Speaker 1: There was no fish when she dropped it off.",
   "Speaker 2: Oh, this is, this is unbelievable. I mean, first you sleep with my ex-girlfriend then you insult my intelligence by lying about it and then you kill my fish, my Buddy?",
   "Speaker 1: Hey I didn't kill your fish. Look Eddie... Would you look at what I'm doin' here. That can't be smart. So we're just gonna take this guy right off ya and put him here in Mr. Pocket. Tangellon?"
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "Buddy",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     31
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:pet"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Buddy",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: Okay, now the Mastodon is from the semi-late Jurassic period.",
   "Speaker 2: Isn’t the Mastodon from the Pliocene Epic?",
   "Speaker 1: Shhh! This is a museum, no talking. Right down here,  Uhh, and over here we have Ross Geller. Everyone wave ‘Hi’ to Ross. Ross is one of our most important scientists, look at him, hard at work. Okay, moving right along. Come on."
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "museum",
    "x": "Ross Geller",
    "rid": [
     28
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:place_of_work"
    ],
    "t": [
     "at work"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "scientist",
    "x": "Ross Geller",
    "rid": [
     29
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:title"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "museum",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     28
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:place_of_work"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "Ross Geller",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: Monica, why don't you finish off these pies? I don't have any more room left in the fridge.",
   "Speaker 2: No. No, thank you!",
   "Speaker 3: Well Judy, you did it! She's finally full!"
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "Judy",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Judy",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: I have sex with dinosaurs??",
   "Speaker 2: I believe I read that somewhere!",
   "Speaker 1: That only is not funny, it's physically impossible! Ok? Depending on the species I'd have to have a six foot long... It's not funny!!",
   "Speaker 2: I respectfully disagree.",
   "Speaker 1: I can't believe you put that on my alumni page!",
   "Speaker 2: Who cares? Nobody reads those things",
   "Speaker 1: You'd better hope not because I just read what you put on your page today.",
   "Speaker 2: I don't have a page.",
   "Speaker 1: Oh oh oh! I RESPECTFULLY DISAGREE!!"
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "Speaker 1",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     4
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alumni"
    ],
    "t": [
     "alumni"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 2",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     4
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alumni"
    ],
    "t": [
     "alumni"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: Good morning!",
   "Speaker 2: Hello. But you know what, hey, new day, new leaf, I am just really really happy ... I'm sorry, obviously Heather's ass has something more important to say so I'll just wait 'till it's finished.",
   "Speaker 3: What?",
   "Speaker 2: I was giving you an apology and you were totally checking her out!",
   "Speaker 3: I wasn't checking her out. I'm in fashion, I was looking at her skirt. Or was it pants? I didn't really see what happened below the ass area.",
   "Speaker 2: Oh wow, you are really, you're really a creep.",
   "Speaker 3: Why do you even care if I was looking at her? Are you jealous?",
   "Speaker 2: Oh yeah, I'm jealous. \"Oh Gavin, please, please look at my ass\". Stop looking at my ass! I mean, I just think you are totally inappropriate, ok? This is a work environment, she's your subordinate.",
   "Speaker 3: I thought it was ok when you slept with your old assistant Tag.",
   "Speaker 2: That is totally different for two reasons. One - I didn't know that you knew that. And two, I wasn't some creep staring at his ass, we had a deep meaningful relationship.",
   "Speaker 3: Huh. What's Tag's last name?",
   "Speaker 2: It was ... oh my god. He didn't have a last name. It was just \"Tag\". You know, like Cher, or, you know, Moses.",
   "Speaker 3: But it was a deep meaningful relationship.",
   "Speaker 2: Oh, you know what - my first impression of you was absolutely right. You are arrogant, you are pompous ... Morgan! Morgan! Tag's last name was Morgan! Huh!",
   "Speaker 3: It was Jones.",
   "Speaker 2: Yeah well what are you, his boyfriend?"
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "Jones",
    "x": "Tag",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "assistant",
    "x": "Tag",
    "rid": [
     29
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:title"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 2",
    "x": "Tag",
    "rid": [
     10,
     5
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:girl/boyfriend",
     "per:boss"
    ],
    "t": [
     "a deep meaningful relationship",
     "assistant"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 3",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     5
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:boss"
    ],
    "t": [
     "subordinate"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Tag",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     10,
     6
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:girl/boyfriend",
     "per:subordinate"
    ],
    "t": [
     "a deep meaningful relationship",
     "assistant"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 3",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     2
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:negative_impression"
    ],
    "t": [
     "arrogant"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 1",
    "x": "Speaker 3",
    "rid": [
     6
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:subordinate"
    ],
    "t": [
     "subordinate"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "a creep",
    "x": "Speaker 3",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: You want me to see a therapist?",
   "Speaker 2: Sweetheart, you obviously have a problem. You've chosen a boyfriend exactly like your father.",
   "Speaker 1: Ok mom, you know what, fine, I'll make an appointment ok, but you know what, right now, I gotta go, I gotta go do a thing.",
   "Speaker 3: Did you know your mother spent $1200 dollars on bansai trees. I felt like Gulliver around that place.",
   "Speaker 1: Daddy, daddy, you know what, I really wanna hear more about this, I really do, but I just have, I just have to do a, some stuff.",
   "Speaker 4: Ok, ok, you can be shirts and I'll be skins. I'll be skins. Hey, how you holdin' up there, tiger? Oh, sorry, when my parents were getting divorced I got a lot of tigers. Got a lot of champs, chiefs, sports, I even got a governor.",
   "Speaker 1: This is it, isn't it? I mean, this is what my life is gonna be like. My mom there, my dad there. Thanksgiving, Christmas. She gets the house, he's in some condo my sister's gonna decorate with wicker. Oh, Chandler how did you get through this?",
   "Speaker 4: Well, I relied on a carefully regimented program of denial and, and wetting the bed.",
   "Speaker 1: Ya know, I just, so weird. I mean I was in there just listening to them bitch about each other and all I kept thinking about was the fourth of July.",
   "Speaker 4: Because it reminded you of the way our forefathers used to bitch at each other?",
   "Speaker 1: It's just this thing. Every year we would go out on my dad's boat and watch the fireworks. Mom always hated it because the ocean air made her hair all big. My sister Jill would be throwing up over the side and my dad would be upset because nobody was helping and then when we did help he would scream at us for doing it wrong. But then when the fireworks started, everybody just shut up, you know, and it'd get really cold, and we would all just sort of smush under this one blanket. It never occured to anybody to bring another one. And now it's just...",
   "Speaker 4: I, I know."
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "Speaker 2",
    "x": "Jill",
    "rid": [
     15
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:parents"
    ],
    "t": [
     "mom"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 1",
    "x": "Jill",
    "rid": [
     16
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:siblings"
    ],
    "t": [
     "sister"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 3",
    "x": "Jill",
    "rid": [
     15
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:parents"
    ],
    "t": [
     "dad"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Jill",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     16
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:siblings"
    ],
    "t": [
     "sister"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "sweetheart",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 2",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     15
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:parents"
    ],
    "t": [
     "mom"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 3",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     15
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:parents"
    ],
    "t": [
     "daddy"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "bitch",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "Jill",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     13
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:children"
    ],
    "t": [
     "mom"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 1",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     13
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:children"
    ],
    "t": [
     "mom"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 3",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     17
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:spouse"
    ],
    "t": [
     "getting divorced"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Jill",
    "x": "Speaker 3",
    "rid": [
     13
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:children"
    ],
    "t": [
     "dad"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 2",
    "x": "Speaker 3",
    "rid": [
     17
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:spouse"
    ],
    "t": [
     "getting divorced"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 1",
    "x": "Speaker 3",
    "rid": [
     13
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:children"
    ],
    "t": [
     "daddy"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: Okay, you come up with an idea.",
   "Speaker 2: Alright alright, we still have three hours till escrow closes on our house. We can still get out.",
   "Speaker 1: But we love our house.",
   "Speaker 2: Will we love it so much with her next door? And she's gonna be louder out here too. Just the crickets and \"Oh My God\"!",
   "Speaker 1: Okay, but if we don't get this house, she's stil gonna show up wherever we go! I mean, at least if she's here, it eliminates the element of surprise. I mean, never again will you have to hear the three words that make your balls jump back up inside your body.",
   "Speaker 2: Well, we have to do something. We can't have her living next door. Oh, that does it too.",
   "Speaker 3: Well... I just talked to Sid, we are definitely putting in an offer on the house... a-a-and I'll bet we get it.",
   "Speaker 2: The Hitlers will be so disappointed.",
   "Speaker 3: All right, I got to run. Tell Monica I say goodbye. And... I'll see you later, neighbor.",
   "Speaker 2: Wait! I just want you to know that... I'm so happy you're going to be here.",
   "Speaker 3: Oh, me too...",
   "Speaker 2: Because... that way... we can pick up where we left off.",
   "Speaker 3: Huh?",
   "Speaker 2: I never stopped loving you.",
   "Speaker 3: Oh... my...",
   "Speaker 2: Yeah, yeah, yeah! I want you... I need you... I must have you Janice Litman Goralnik Neihosenstein.",
   "Speaker 3: Chandler, what are you talking about?",
   "Speaker 2: Now that you live next door, we can be together every day. Sid and Monica never have to know a thing.",
   "Speaker 3: I don't know what to say... I mean, you know, obviously we have this... heat between us.",
   "Speaker 2: Obviously.",
   "Speaker 3: But I love my husband. And I know you love your wife. Now, I don't think we should get this house now.",
   "Speaker 2: Don't say that. Don't tangle the dream and take it away.",
   "Speaker 3: Chandler, one of us has got to be strong.",
   "Speaker 2: I understand.",
   "Speaker 3: Although, maybe just... one last moment of weakness... Goodbye Chandler Bing.",
   "Speaker 2: They're never coming down now."
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "Speaker 3",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     2
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:negative_impression"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Chandler Bing",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     17
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:spouse"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 2",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     17
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:spouse"
    ],
    "t": [
     "wife"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 2",
    "x": "Speaker 3",
    "rid": [
     10
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:girl/boyfriend"
    ],
    "t": [
     "pick up where we left off"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Janice Litman Goralnik Neihosenstein",
    "x": "Speaker 3",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Sid",
    "x": "Speaker 3",
    "rid": [
     17,
     1
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:spouse",
     "per:positive_impression"
    ],
    "t": [
     "husband",
     "love"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 1",
    "x": "Chandler Bing",
    "rid": [
     17
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:spouse"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 1",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     17
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:spouse"
    ],
    "t": [
     "wife"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 3",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     10,
     2
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:girl/boyfriend",
     "per:negative_impression"
    ],
    "t": [
     "pick up where we left off",
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Chandler Bing",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "neighbor",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 3",
    "x": "Sid",
    "rid": [
     17
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:spouse"
    ],
    "t": [
     "husband"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: Hey Chandler! Saw the new furniture. Very nice.",
   "Speaker 2: Yeah! Joey has the best boyfriend ever!",
   "Speaker 3: I kissed Kathy.",
   "Speaker 1: What?",
   "Speaker 2: Are you serious?",
   "Speaker 4: Does Joey know?",
   "Speaker 3: No. Is there anyway, anyway you think he'll understand this?",
   "Speaker 2: You obviously haven't screwed over a lot of your friends. Which we all appreciate.",
   "Speaker 1: No the-the sad thing is, if you had told him how you felt before you kissed her, knowing Joey, he probably just would've just stepped aside.",
   "Speaker 3: Oh, don't say that! Don't say that. That's not true. Is it?",
   "Speaker 4: I think maybe, yeah.",
   "Speaker 2: He loves you.",
   "Speaker 3: Then why didn't you tell me to do that?!!",
   "Speaker 1: Well, I said-I said something to Phoebe.",
   "Speaker 4: Yeah! No, that's right. And I thought it was a really good idea.",
   "Speaker 5: I know, I remember that!",
   "Speaker 2: I remember you did.",
   "Speaker 3: God!! What am I gonna do?!",
   "Speaker 5: Well, Chandler, you're gonna have to tell him.",
   "Speaker 3: Why?! Why do I have to tell him?!",
   "Speaker 5: Because you do.",
   "Speaker 3: Yeah, I know.",
   "Speaker 1: Hey, would it be okay if I wrote a song about this."
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "Joey",
    "x": "Speaker 3",
    "rid": [
     9
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:friends"
    ],
    "t": [
     "boyfriend"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 3",
    "x": "Joey",
    "rid": [
     9,
     1
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:friends",
     "per:positive_impression"
    ],
    "t": [
     "boyfriend",
     "loves"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: All right, I have one question. What is the deal with this?",
   "Speaker 2: Bye-bye little puppet Joey hand?",
   "Speaker 1: No, the quiet down thing!",
   "Speaker 2: You mean this.",
   "Speaker 1: Um-hmm! Look, I-I-I don't know how much more of this I can take! Did you know he taped over my Baywatch tape with some show about bugs! My God! What if that had been porn?",
   "Speaker 2: All right look, y'know, this maybe tough but come on, this is Ross! I survived college with him!",
   "Speaker 1: All right, I guess I can hold out a little longer. Let's have a game.",
   "Speaker 2: Okay."
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "Ross",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     4
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alumni"
    ],
    "t": [
     "survived college with"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 2",
    "x": "Ross",
    "rid": [
     4
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alumni"
    ],
    "t": [
     "survived college with"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: Hey guys! Hey!",
   "Speaker 2: Hey Pheebs, guess who we saw today.",
   "Speaker 3: Ooh, ooh, fun! Okay... um, Liam Neeson.",
   "Speaker 2: Nope.",
   "Speaker 3: Morly Safer.",
   "Speaker 2: Nope.",
   "Speaker 3: The woman who cuts my hair!",
   "Speaker 4: Okay, look, this could be a really long game.",
   "Speaker 5: Your sister Ursula.",
   "Speaker 3: Oh, really.",
   "Speaker 5: Yeah, yeah, she works over at that place, uh...",
   "Speaker 3: Rift’s. Yeah, I know.",
   "Speaker 5: Oh, you do? Because she said you guys haven’t talked in like years.",
   "Speaker 3: Hmmm? Yeah. So, um, is she fat?",
   "Speaker 2: Not from where I was standin’.",
   "Speaker 3:  where were you standing?",
   "Speaker 6: Um, Pheebs, so, you guys just don’t get along?",
   "Speaker 3: It’s mostly just dumb sister stuff, you know, I mean, like, everyone always thought of her as the pretty one, you know... Oh, oh, she was the first one to start walking, even though I did it... later that same day. But, to my parents, by then it was like \"yeah, right, well what else is new?\""
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "Ursula",
    "x": "Pheebs",
    "rid": [
     16
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:siblings"
    ],
    "t": [
     "sister"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Pheebs",
    "x": "Ursula",
    "rid": [
     16
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:siblings"
    ],
    "t": [
     "sister"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Rift’s",
    "x": "Ursula",
    "rid": [
     22
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:employee_or_member_of"
    ],
    "t": [
     "works over at"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "ORG"
   },
   {
    "y": "Pheebs",
    "x": "Speaker 6",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Pheebs",
    "x": "Speaker 3",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Ursula",
    "x": "Speaker 3",
    "rid": [
     2
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:negative_impression"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Ursula",
    "x": "Rift’s",
    "rid": [
     35
    ],
    "r": [
     "org:employees_or_members"
    ],
    "t": [
     "works over at"
    ],
    "x_type": "ORG",
    "y_type": "PER"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: Hi!",
   "Speaker 2: Hi.",
   "Speaker 1: Oh, I’m so glad you called. I feel like it’s always me calling you. So, what’s up? Is everything okay with Phoebe?",
   "Speaker 2: It will be…in a minute. Listen, Tim you’re a really great guy.",
   "Speaker 1: It’s because I’m with you.",
   "Speaker 2: Aw. I’m just—I’m in a place in my life right now where I…I…",
   "Speaker 1: Whoops. Sorry. This just in. Oh, it’s 9-1-1 from the restaurant, that means Monica needs me right away.",
   "Speaker 2: Oh-oh no she doesn’t! I know what that is. You can stay.",
   "Speaker 1: Awww, I’ll miss you too Pheebs. And I will be holding you, right here."
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "Speaker 2",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     1,
     10
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:positive_impression",
     "per:girl/boyfriend"
    ],
    "t": [
     "",
     "with"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Pheebs",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 1",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     10
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:girl/boyfriend"
    ],
    "t": [
     "with"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: Hey guys.",
   "Speaker 2, Speaker 3, Speaker 4: Hey.",
   "Speaker 2: What's in the bag?",
   "Speaker 1: Um, just some presents.",
   "Speaker 4: C'mon show us what you bought. . . You know you want to.",
   "Speaker 1: OK. OK, this is a picture frame from Ben to my parents, huh.",
   "Speaker 3: Cute.",
   "Speaker 1: I got some, uh, hers and hers towels for Susan and Carol. And, uh, I got this blouse for mom.",
   "Speaker 3: Ross, that is gorgeous!",
   "Speaker 1: Yeah?",
   "Speaker 3: Look at these authentic fake medals. I tell ya, mom's gonna be voted best dressed at the make-believe military academy."
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "Speaker 1",
    "x": "Speaker 3",
    "rid": [
     16
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:siblings"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Susan",
    "x": "Carol",
    "rid": [
     10
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:girl/boyfriend"
    ],
    "t": [
     "hers and hers"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 3",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     16
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:siblings"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Carol",
    "x": "Susan",
    "rid": [
     10
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:girl/boyfriend"
    ],
    "t": [
     "hers and hers"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: Ross.",
   "Speaker 2: Yeah?",
   "Speaker 1: Can I ask you something?",
   "Speaker 2: Uh-huh.",
   "Speaker 1: When Carol was pregnant with Ben…",
   "Speaker 2: Mmm?",
   "Speaker 1: …were you this irritating?",
   "Speaker 2: Wow!",
   "Speaker 1: Excuse me?!",
   "Speaker 2: Oh nothing. Nothing! Just uh, you’ve been a little short with me lately. I’m not trying to irritate you.",
   "Speaker 1: Well then you just must have a natural talent for it.",
   "Speaker 2: Y’know what? The doctor will be in soon, why don’t we not speak until then.",
   "Speaker 1: Okay. Seriously, breathe louder Ross! That’s great!",
   "Speaker 2: Y’know we should probably ask the doctor if she even knows how to deliver a baby that’s half human and half pure evil!"
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "Ben",
    "x": "Carol",
    "rid": [
     15
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:parents"
    ],
    "t": [
     "pregnant with"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Carol",
    "x": "Ben",
    "rid": [
     13
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:children"
    ],
    "t": [
     "pregnant with"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: Hey, Lizzie.",
   "Speaker 2: Hey, Weird Girl.",
   "Speaker 1: I brought you alphabet soup.",
   "Speaker 2: Did you pick out the vowels?",
   "Speaker 1: Yes. But I left in the Ys. 'Cause, y'know, \"sometimes y\". Uh, I also have something else for you.",
   "Speaker 2: Saltines?",
   "Speaker 1: No, but would you like a thousand dollars and a football phone?",
   "Speaker 2: What? Oh my God, there's really money in here.",
   "Speaker 1: I know.",
   "Speaker 2: Weird Girl, what are you doing?",
   "Speaker 1: No, I want you to have it. I don't want it.",
   "Speaker 2: No, no, I ha-I have to give you something.",
   "Speaker 1: Oh, that's fine, no.",
   "Speaker 2: Would you like my tin-foil hat?",
   "Speaker 1: No. 'Cause you need that. No, it's okay, thanks.",
   "Speaker 2: Please, let me do something.",
   "Speaker 1: Okay, alright, you buy me a soda, and then we're even. Okay?",
   "Speaker 2: Okay.",
   "Speaker 1: Okay."
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "Speaker 1",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     3
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:acquaintance"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 2",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     3
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:acquaintance"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Weird Girl",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: Okay... aahhh... Please laugh for mommy... Please? Please laugh for mommy... Not funny huh? Oh so, is it... only offensive novelty rap? Or maybe just, you know, rap in general? 'Cause mommy can rap... My name is mommy and I'm here to say / that all the babies are... Oh, I can't rap... All right sweetheart... This is only because I love you so much, and I know that you're not gonna tell anybody... I like... big butts and I cannot lie... / You other brothers can't deny... / when a girl walks in with an itty bitty waist and a round thing in your face... Yes! Yes! Yes! YES! Oohhhhh! Oh!  I like big butts and I cannot lie... / You other brothers can't deny... Oh Emma you're laughing! Oh you are, you really do like big butts, don't you. Oh you beautiful little weirdo...",
   "Speaker 2: Hey!",
   "Speaker 1: Oh you missed it. She was laughing. Oh it was amazing. It was amazing. It was the most beautiful, beautiful sound that...",
   "Speaker 2: Oh I know, isn't it? Ooh... what'd you do to get her to laugh?",
   "Speaker 1: Oh! You know, I just... couple of things I tried ... I just sang a little doo... Itsy Bitsy Spider...",
   "Speaker 2: You sang Baby Got Back didn't you?",
   "Speaker 1: Nothing else worked. That girl is all about the ass..."
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "mommy",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "Emma",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     13,
     1
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:children",
     "per:positive_impression"
    ],
    "t": [
     "mommy",
     "love"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "sweetheart",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "sweetheart",
    "x": "Emma",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 1",
    "x": "Emma",
    "rid": [
     15
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:parents"
    ],
    "t": [
     "mommy"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "beautiful little weirdo",
    "x": "Emma",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "Baby Got Back",
    "x": "Emma",
    "rid": [
     1
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:positive_impression"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "Baby",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "sweetheart",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: Dr. Geller, Sherman Whitfield, London Institute.",
   "Speaker 2: Wow! What a pleasure.",
   "Speaker 3: Well, I have to tell you, I was quite impressed with your paper on Pre-Cretaceous fossils. Yeah, it confirmed everything that I have written.",
   "Speaker 4: Excuse me. Hi.",
   "Speaker 3: Yes?",
   "Speaker 4: Well, your kind of sitting in my seat.",
   "Speaker 3: What do you mean, your seat?",
   "Speaker 4: I mean, I was sitting there.",
   "Speaker 3: But, you got up!",
   "Speaker 4: But, I never left the room!",
   "Speaker 3: But, you left the chair area.",
   "Speaker 4: All right, that's it, give me your underwear."
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "Speaker 1",
    "x": "London Institute",
    "rid": [
     35
    ],
    "r": [
     "org:employees_or_members"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "ORG",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Dr. Geller",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "London Institute",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     22
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:employee_or_member_of"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "ORG"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: Hey.",
   "Speaker 2, Speaker 3: Hey.",
   "Speaker 1: Is ah, is Chandler around?",
   "Speaker 3: No, umm, he met some girl at the coffee house.",
   "Speaker 1: Oooh.",
   "Speaker 3: Yeah, Ginger something.",
   "Speaker 1: Nooo. No, no, ah, are you sure it wasn’t something that sounded like Ginger, like ah, Gingeer?",
   "Speaker 3: No, it was Ginger. I remember, because when he told me, I said, ‘the movie star.’",
   "Speaker 1: Aww, man. That’s the girl I was hiding from. When she finds out he’s my roommate, she’s gonna tell him what I did.",
   "Speaker 3: Well, what did you do?",
   "Speaker 1: What, oh, oh, oh, no, no, I can’t, I can’t tell you that, it’s like the most awful, horrible thing I’ve ever done my whole life.",
   "Speaker 3: Y'know what, don’t tell us. We’ll just wait until Chandler gets home, because it’ll be more fun that way.",
   "Speaker 1: All right!! Okay, it was like four years ago. Okay, Ginger and I had gone out a few times, and then this one weekend, we went up to her Dad’s cabin. Just me, her, and her annoying little dog Pepper. Well that night, I cooked this really romantic dinner....",
   "Speaker 3: You gave her food poisoning!?",
   "Speaker 1: I wish. No. After dinner, me, her, and Pepper all fell asleep in front of the fire. Well I woke up in the middle of the night and I saw that the fire was dying out. So, I picked up a log and threw it on. Or, at least what I thought was a log.",
   "Speaker 2: Oh my God!! You threw Pepper on the fire!",
   "Speaker 1: I wish. See, I guess another thing I probably should’ve told you about Ginger is that she kinda has a ah, artificial leg.",
   "Speaker 3: Oh my God! Joey, what did you do after you threw her leg on the fire?",
   "Speaker 1: I ran!!"
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "man",
    "x": "Speaker 3",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "man",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "man",
    "x": "Chandler",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 1",
    "x": "Chandler",
    "rid": [
     12
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:roommate"
    ],
    "t": [
     "roommate"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Pepper",
    "x": "Ginger",
    "rid": [
     31
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:pet"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Dad",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "girl",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "Chandler",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     12
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:roommate"
    ],
    "t": [
     "roommate"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "man",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: Oh hey Ross, oh I'm so glad someone's here. Could you zip me up?",
   "Speaker 2: Sure.",
   "Speaker 1: Thank you. Can you believe no one between my apartment and here offered to do that for me?.",
   "Speaker 2: People. So why you all dressed up?",
   "Speaker 1: Oh umm. Mike's picking me up for a date.",
   "Speaker 2: Oh yea? Now um, how is that going, is it getting serious?",
   "Speaker 1: Oh I dunno, I dunno, you know I mean, I like him but am I ready to take my grade-A loins off the meat market?",
   "Speaker 2: You know, I really admire your whole dating attitude, it's so healthy. I'm always like, is this moving to fast? Is this moving to slow? Where's this going?",
   "Speaker 1: Yeah, you know, you are a bit of a drama queen.",
   "Speaker 2: But you, you're so much better off. You just go from guy to guy having fun and never worrying that it terms into anything serious.",
   "Speaker 1: I wouldn't say never, you know. There's that guy ... well what about...OK well there's gotta be someone.",
   "Speaker 2: There isn't. That's what I'm saying.",
   "Speaker 1: Oh my God, you're right!",
   "Speaker 2: I know, and yet here you are, all ready for the next date.",
   "Speaker 1: I can't believe I never realized this before. I'm in my 30s and never been in a long-term relationship! Oh my God! What's wrong with me?",
   "Speaker 2: No, no, no there's nothing wrong with you. I mean, you don't strike me as the type of person that wants to get married anyway.",
   "Speaker 1: I wanna get married!",
   "Speaker 2: Please don't cry because of me, Pheebs. I don't know what I'm talking about. I've been divorced three times!",
   "Speaker 1: At least you've been married! Oh my God! I wanna trade lives with Ross!"
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "Speaker 1",
    "x": "Mike",
    "rid": [
     8
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:dates"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Pheebs",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Mike",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     8,
     1
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:dates",
     "per:positive_impression"
    ],
    "t": [
     "",
     "like"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "drama queen",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: Isn’t it incredible?! Monica and Chandler, gettin’ married.",
   "Speaker 2: I know, they’re gonna be so happy together.",
   "Speaker 1: Ohh… I mean two best friends falling in love, how often does that happen?",
   "Speaker 2: Not that often!",
   "Speaker 1: No! I’m so happy for them!",
   "Speaker 2: Me too! So happy for them!",
   "Speaker 1: I’m so happy and not at all jealous.",
   "Speaker 2: Oh no! No God, definitely not jealous!",
   "Speaker 1: I mean I’m probably 98% happy, maybe 2% jealous. And I mean what’s 2%? That’s nothing.",
   "Speaker 2: Totally. I’m like 90/10.",
   "Speaker 1: Yeah me too."
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "Chandler",
    "x": "Monica",
    "rid": [
     10,
     9
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:girl/boyfriend",
     "per:friends"
    ],
    "t": [
     "falling in love",
     "best friends"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Monica",
    "x": "Chandler",
    "rid": [
     10,
     9
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:girl/boyfriend",
     "per:friends"
    ],
    "t": [
     "falling in love",
     "best friends"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: Look at that face! Just like when you were in high school! If I didn’t know better I’d say you were a cheerleader in trouble. Come on, let’s get some tea.",
   "Speaker 2: Okay.",
   "Speaker 1: Oh my look at that. Only three weeks to go, now have you picked your nanny yet? Now I don’t want you to use your housekeeper ‘cause it would just split her focus.",
   "Speaker 2: Oh well actually gonna use a nanny and uh, I don’t even have a housekeeper.",
   "Speaker 1: It’s like you’re a cave person. Rachel, you must get a nanny. You don’t know how overwhelming this is going to be. I mean when you were a baby I had full time help, I had Mrs. Kay.",
   "Speaker 2: Mrs. Kay! Oh yeah, she was sweet. She taught me Spanish. I actually think I remember some of it, tu madre es loca.",
   "Speaker 1: Such a sweet woman.",
   "Speaker 2: Well, however great she was I just can’t afford that.",
   "Speaker 1: Oh Rachel!",
   "Speaker 2: What?",
   "Speaker 1: I just had the greatest idea! I’m gonna come live with you!",
   "Speaker 2: Wh-wh-what? What?",
   "Speaker 1: Oh, I’m so happy I’m gonna do this for my little girl. Aw, look at you. You have tears in your eyes.",
   "Speaker 2: Yes. Yes I do."
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "baby",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "little girl",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "Mrs. Kay",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     1
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:positive_impression"
    ],
    "t": [
     "sweet"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Mrs. Kay",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     1
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:positive_impression"
    ],
    "t": [
     "sweet"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "nanny",
    "x": "Mrs. Kay",
    "rid": [
     29
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:title"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: I’m not here! That’s just my Chinese food!",
   "Speaker 2: Oh, my God! She has food delivered here?",
   "Speaker 3: Mm-hmm. She’s—she’s emotional, but, but ballsy.",
   "Speaker 1: You know what I’m going to do? I’m going to get in my sweats, and eat this in bed!",
   "Speaker 3: And you thought she was going to be in our way! So, why don’t you, uh, open the champagne, and I’ll be right back. I’ve got a surprise for you.",
   "Speaker 2: You got another ex-wife back there?",
   "Speaker 3: Please start drinking!",
   "Speaker 1: I’m just going to grab the phone.",
   "Speaker 2: Oh, Rachel! Wait! Hey, I hope you don’t take this the wrong way, but, but, um… what are you doing?",
   "Speaker 1: Oh, I’m sorry! Do you need the phone?",
   "Speaker 2: No, no. Listen, Ross is too nice to say anything, but this is his apartment, and, and, we gotta have some boundaries, so why don’t you go back to your place and give us some privacy?",
   "Speaker 1: But, but, Mona, I live here.",
   "Speaker 3: Happy Valentine’s Day! …Or something to remember me by."
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "Speaker 1",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     2
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:negative_impression"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 3",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     12,
     17
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:roommate",
     "per:spouse"
    ],
    "t": [
     "live",
     "ex-wife"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 1",
    "x": "Speaker 3",
    "rid": [
     17,
     12
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:spouse",
     "per:roommate"
    ],
    "t": [
     "ex-wife",
     "live"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: Hi.",
   "Speaker 2: Hi.",
   "Speaker 1: Guess what?",
   "Speaker 2: What?",
   "Speaker 1: They published my paper.",
   "Speaker 2: Oh, really, let me see, let me see.",
   "Speaker 3: Rach, look! Oh, hi! Where is my strong Ross Skywalker to come rescue me. There he is."
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "Rach",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Ross Skywalker",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: Hey hey hey! She's on!",
   "Speaker 2: Ah! Nora Bing!",
   "Speaker 3: ...Now what is this about you-you being arrested i-in London? What is that all about?",
   "Speaker 1: Your mom was arrested?",
   "Speaker 4: Shhh, busy beaming with pride.",
   "Speaker 5: ...This is kind of embarrassing, but occasionally after I've been intimate with a man...",
   "Speaker 4: Now why would she say that's embarrassing?",
   "Speaker 6: Shhh.",
   "Speaker 5: ...I just get this craving for Kung Pow Chicken.",
   "Speaker 4: THAT'S TOO MUCH INFORMATION!!",
   "Speaker 3: Alright, so now you're doing this whole book tour thing, how is that going?",
   "Speaker 5: Oh, fine. I'm leaving for New York tomorrow, which I hate- but I get to see my son, who I love...",
   "Speaker 6: Awww!",
   "Speaker 4: This is the way that I find out. Most moms use the phone."
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "Nora Bing",
    "x": "Speaker 5",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 4",
    "x": "Speaker 5",
    "rid": [
     1,
     13
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:positive_impression",
     "per:children"
    ],
    "t": [
     "love",
     "moms"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 4",
    "x": "New York",
    "rid": [
     32
    ],
    "r": [
     "gpe:residents_of_place"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "GPE",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 5",
    "x": "Speaker 4",
    "rid": [
     15
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:parents"
    ],
    "t": [
     "moms"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "New York",
    "x": "Speaker 4",
    "rid": [
     18
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:place_of_residence"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "GPE"
   },
   {
    "y": "man",
    "x": "Speaker 4",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: You’ve never asked a guy out?!!",
   "Speaker 2: No. Have you?",
   "Speaker 1: Thousands of times!! That doesn’t make me sound too good does it?",
   "Speaker 2: I don’t even know how I would go about it.",
   "Speaker 3: Oh-oh-oh-oh, how I do it is, I look a woman up and down and say, \"Hey, how you doin’?\"",
   "Speaker 1: Oh, please!",
   "Speaker 3: Hey, how you doin’?",
   "Speaker 2: You know what, I’m gonna do that, I’m gonna call him up, and I’m gonna ask him out. I can do that. Ask him out. How you doin’? Hi! Joshua? It’s Rachel Green from Bloomingdale’s. Yeah, umm, I was wondering if you umm, if you umm, left your wallet at the store today? Well, we found a wallet, and we—the license? Well, that is a good idea! Uh, well, let’s see here this says this license belongs to a uh, uh, belongs to a mister uh, Pheebs, and umm, yeah, so sorry to bother you at home. I’ll see you tomorrow. Bye. You’ve done that a thousand times?",
   "Speaker 1: I’ve never done that.",
   "Speaker 2: Ohh, God, I just got so nervous that he would say no.",
   "Speaker 3: Well, you gotta give him something that he can’t say no too. Like uh, Knicks tickets! Invite the guy to a Knicks game, you’re guaranteed he’ll say yes!",
   "Speaker 2: Really?! You think that will work?",
   "Speaker 3: Absolutely! And if it doesn’t, can I get the extra ticket?",
   "Speaker 4: Rachel, one of your customers seems to have left his billfold. A Joshua Bergen.",
   "Speaker 2: Really?",
   "Speaker 4: Will you call him?",
   "Speaker 2: Yes! I will! Absolutely! Hello, Rachel. Hi, Joshua. I left my wallet here on purpose. Really? Yes, I just wanted to see you again. Oh, I’m glad. Rachel, I’d like to say something to you. Yes? How you doin’?"
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "Joshua Bergen",
    "x": "Joshua",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Rachel Green",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Joshua",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     1
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:positive_impression"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Joshua Bergen",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     7
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:client"
    ],
    "t": [
     "customers"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Bloomingdale’s",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     22
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:employee_or_member_of"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "ORG"
   },
   {
    "y": "Pheebs",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 2",
    "x": "Bloomingdale’s",
    "rid": [
     35
    ],
    "r": [
     "org:employees_or_members"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "ORG",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Rachel Green",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Pheebs",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Knicks",
    "x": "Speaker 3",
    "rid": [
     1
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:positive_impression"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "ORG"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: Uhh, excuse me is there a Mr. Bowmont at this table?",
   "Speaker 2: That’s me.",
   "Speaker 1: Ahh, yes.",
   "Speaker 3: Oh well, hello. This is your lucky day Mr. Bowmont, the uh gentleman day sailer as just become available again and I believe that you made a bid of $18,000.",
   "Speaker 1: You-you have to pay that! It’s not just a guess.",
   "Speaker 3: Okay. Okay.",
   "Speaker 2: I was actually relieved uh I didn’t win the boat. My wife would’ve killed me.",
   "Speaker 3: Ohh…",
   "Speaker 1: Are you kidding me?! She’s gonna this boat!",
   "Speaker 3: Y-Yeah! What-what is your wife’s name?",
   "Speaker 2: It’s Pam.",
   "Speaker 3: Pam! Oh God okay, just imagine this, \"The Pam.\"",
   "Speaker 1: Aw-awww!",
   "Speaker 2: I don’t think she’d like that.",
   "Speaker 3: Okay, uh-uh imagine this, \"The Mr. Bowmont.\"",
   "Speaker 1: Oooooh…",
   "Speaker 2: I don’t think so dear.",
   "Speaker 3: Okay look, let me paint you a little picture. All right, you are settin’ sail up the Hudson! You’ve got the wind in your h——arms! You-you get all that peace and quiet that you’ve always wanted! You get back to nature! You can go fishin’! You can—ooh, you can get one of those little hats and have people call you captain, and then when you’re old, Cappy.",
   "Speaker 2: What the hell, it’s for a good cause! All right!",
   "Speaker 1: No way! It’s mine!!",
   "Speaker 3: What?! What?!",
   "Speaker 1: All that stuff you just said? I want that!",
   "Speaker 3: But Joey you don’t have $20,000!",
   "Speaker 1: Who cares?! I-I’ll make payments, whatever it takes, I want the Mr. Bowmont!!"
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "Pam",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     17
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:spouse"
    ],
    "t": [
     "wife"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "dear",
    "x": "Speaker 3",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 2",
    "x": "Pam",
    "rid": [
     17
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:spouse"
    ],
    "t": [
     "wife"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "captain",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: Wow! It looks like you were very generous with your grades this semester!",
   "Speaker 2: Professor Geller?",
   "Speaker 3: Yeah?",
   "Speaker 2: I wanted to say how much I enjoyed your class.",
   "Speaker 3: Oh thank you. Thanks very much.",
   "Speaker 2: Uh, I’m a little embarrassed about calling you a hottie on my evaluation…",
   "Speaker 3: That was you?",
   "Speaker 2: Yeah. I felt a little weird about it. You’re a teacher. I’m a student. But would you maybe want to go out with me sometime?",
   "Speaker 3: Oh I, I don’t-I don’t think that would be the best idea.",
   "Speaker 2: Oh, because I was thinking, the semester’s over; you’re not my teacher anymore.",
   "Speaker 3: What time?",
   "Speaker 2: Oh, y’know what? Forget it, you already gave me an A.",
   "Speaker 3: Gotcha.",
   "Speaker 2: I’m kidding!",
   "Speaker 3: Oh! So-so seriously, what time?"
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "Speaker 3",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     1
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:positive_impression"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Professor Geller",
    "x": "Speaker 3",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "professor",
    "x": "Speaker 3",
    "rid": [
     29
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:title"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "teacher",
    "x": "Speaker 3",
    "rid": [
     29
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:title"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "hottie",
    "x": "Speaker 3",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: Oh, honey, honey, tell them the story about your patient who thinks things are, like, other things. Y'know? Like, the phone rings and she takes a shower.",
   "Speaker 2: That's pretty much it.",
   "Speaker 1: Oops!",
   "Speaker 2: But you tell it really well, sweetie.",
   "Speaker 1: Thanks. Okay, now go away so we can talk about you.",
   "Speaker 2: Okay. I'll miss you."
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "honey",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 1",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     10
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:girl/boyfriend"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "honey",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 2",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     10
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:girl/boyfriend"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "sweetie",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: Guess whose middle name is Muriel.",
   "Speaker 2: Chandler M. Bing?",
   "Speaker 1: Yeah-ha!",
   "Speaker 2: Oh my God.",
   "Speaker 1: I’m sorry about your date.",
   "Speaker 2: Oh it’s all right. I’m guess I’m just done with the whole dating thing. It’s one more thing in my life that’s suddenly completely different. This is hard.",
   "Speaker 1: Yeah I know. On the other hand in um, in about seven months you’re gonna have something that you’re gonna love more than any guy you’ve ever gone out with. Just wait. Wait until uh, wait until the first time your baby grabs your finger. You have no idea.",
   "Speaker 2: Thanks sweetie.",
   "Speaker 1: You wanna, you wanna grab some coffee?",
   "Speaker 2: Oh no, I think I’m gonna go home and eat ten candy bars.",
   "Speaker 1: Hey, I thought I cheered you up.",
   "Speaker 2: Oh you did, there are twenty in here.",
   "Speaker 1: Right. Good night.",
   "Speaker 2: Good night."
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "baby",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "sweetie",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "baby",
    "x": "Chandler",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "sweetie",
    "x": "Chandler",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "baby",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "sweetie",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: Hello? Oh, hi Ross! See? Other people call me!",
   "Speaker 2: Ooh, your brother. Score!",
   "Speaker 1: What’s up?",
   "Speaker 3: Oh, I’m just over here with Ben. I thought we’d say hi.",
   "Speaker 1: Oh, put him on!",
   "Speaker 3: Ben, say hi to Aunt Monica. Oh, I guess he doesn’t feel like talking right now. He’s smiling though! Okay, talk to you later.",
   "Speaker 3: Hello? Hey Mon, how’s the packing going? Ben? He’s fine. Yeah, he’s right—Oh my God! Get your head of your shirt there son! What? Yeah, it’s a pumpkin. I’ll come pack."
  ],
  [
   {
    "y": "Aunt Monica",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Ben",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     14
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:other_family"
    ],
    "t": [
     "Aunt"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Mon",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     30
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:alternate_names"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 3",
    "x": "Speaker 1",
    "rid": [
     16
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:siblings"
    ],
    "t": [
     "brother"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "pumpkin",
    "x": "Speaker 2",
    "rid": [
     37
    ],
    "r": [
     "unanswerable"
    ],
    "t": [
     ""
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "STRING"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 1",
    "x": "Ben",
    "rid": [
     14
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:other_family"
    ],
    "t": [
     "Aunt"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 3",
    "x": "Ben",
    "rid": [
     15
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:parents"
    ],
    "t": [
     "son"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Speaker 1",
    "x": "Speaker 3",
    "rid": [
     16
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:siblings"
    ],
    "t": [
     "brother"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   },
   {
    "y": "Ben",
    "x": "Speaker 3",
    "rid": [
     13
    ],
    "r": [
     "per:children"
    ],
    "t": [
     "son"
    ],
    "x_type": "PER",
    "y_type": "PER"
   }
  ]
 ],
 [
  [
   "Speaker 1: Hey, Pheebs!",
   "Speaker 2: Hey.",
   "Speaker 1: Hey, how’s it going?",
   "Speaker 2: Well, I’ve got to get out of this bed, I’m going crazy here. Crazy!",
   "Speaker 3: Here you go sweetie.",
   "Speaker 2: What the hell is this, herbal tea? I hate herbal tea!",
   "Speaker 3: But, I put some honey in it.",
